(WIND BLOWING)
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
He's okay.
Rocket.
Very good job!
That's how...
That's how... we'll get away.
(GASPING)
Go find your mother.
For the radio?
Might help us boost the signal.
For you.
Thank you.
It'll be dark soon.
Listen to me...
Too loud.
(BIRDS CAWING)
(TOY BEEPING)
(TOY WHIRRING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(BRANCHES SNAPPING)
(WIND BLOWING)
(RADIO STATIC CRACKLING)
S.
S.O.
S.O.S.
S.
S.O.
S.O.S.
(SIZZLING)
(EXHALES)
Dinner.
REGAN: (WHISPERING) One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(BIRDS SCREECHING AND FLYING AWAY)
(LOUD CRASHING)
(METAL CREAKING)
(METAL GROANING)
(SHRIEKING)
(EXHALES)
(MOUTHING) I'm sorry.
(RACCOONS CHITTERING)
(SQUEALS)
(FEEDBACK WHINING)
Beautiful.
I didn't say anything.
(MUSIC PLAYING THROUGH HEADPHONES)
(PUMPING)
(FETAL HEART BEATING)
You cannot go down there!
Why not?
You know why.
I'm not a child! I won't make a sound!
Just don't.
Please.
This time, I took small amplifiers from the stereo.
It.
It. Won't.
It. Won't. Work.
No, this should increase the frequency to...
It.
It. Never.
It. Never. Works!
But...
we'll keep trying
until it does.
(LEE SIGHS)
Stop.
Just
(SOBS)
Remember, you need to divide.
Carry the three.
Amazing!
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Time to go.
...please don't make me go...
You'll be fine.
Your father will always protect you.
Your father will always protect you. Always.
Listen to me...
It's important that you learn these things.
He just wants you to be able to take care of yourself.
...to take care of me.
...when I'm old...
...and grey...
...and I have no teeth...
(WHISPERING) Don't worry.
I don't want to go.
There's nothing to be scared of.
...of course there is.
I'll go.
I need you to stay and help your mother.
I want to go.
Just stay here.
You'll be safe.
...next time.
(MUFFLED THUD)
(LIGHT FEEDBACK WHINING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(WHISPERING)
They'll hear you.
Look at me.
Listen.
The river...
The river... is loud.
Small sounds...
Small sounds... safe.
Big sounds...
Big sounds... not safe.
Unless...
there's another sound nearby...
there's another sound nearby... that's louder.
You're safe.
I wanna show you something.
(GASPS)
(EXHALES)
(WATERFALL ROARING)
(HOOTS LOUDLY)
(ALOUD) Hey,
you're all right.
You're all right.
I promise.
(MUFFLED HOOT)
(ALOUD) Why didn't you let her come?
Do you blame her
for what happened?
No.
Because she blames herself.
(SNIFFLES)
It was no one's fault.
You still love her, right?
Of course I do.
(NO SOUNDS)
You should tell her.
(FAINT CREAKING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(SCREAMS)
(RUSTLING)
(CLACKING)
(SNARLING AND GROWLING)
(CREATURE SCREECHING)
(WHIMPERING SOFTLY)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(GROANS)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(SOBBING QUIETLY)
(SHUDDERS)
(CREATURE SCREECHING)
(CLACKING)
(CRASHING)
(STIFLED MOAN)
(EXHALING)
(CLACKING)
(GROWLING AND CLACKING)
(CREAKING)
(SNARLS)
(HISSING AND CLACKING)
(GROWLING)
(CLACKING)
(STIFLED SOB)
(TIMER TICKING)
(TIMER BELL RINGING)
(GROWLING AND SNARLING)
(CREATURE SHRIEKING)
(CLACKING)
Rocket.
I need you...
I need you... to make a sound...
I need you... to make a sound... that's louder.
Your mother...
Your mother... needs your help.
You.
You. Can.
You. Can. Do this.
(SIGHS)
(STIFLED MOAN)
(SHUDDERING)
- (RUSTLING)
- (GASPS)
(GROWLING)
(NEARBY RUSTLING)
(STIFLED MOANS)
(CLACKING)
(LOUD WHISTLING AND EXPLOSION)
(CREATURE ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
(EXPLOSIONS)
(WHISTLING AND EXPLOSIONS CONTINUING)
(INHALES)
(EXHALES)
(BABY COOING)
(PANTING)
(BRANCHES SNAPPING)
(CREATURE SCREECHING)
(GROWLING)
(BABY COOING)
(BABY FUSSES)
(BABY CRYING)
(WAILING LOUDLY)
(BABY CONTINUES FUSSING)
- (MUFFLED ROARS OVERHEAD)
- LEE: Shh...
(BABY CONTINUES FUSSING)
(OXYGEN TANK HISSING)
(GROWLING OVERHEAD)
(MUFFLED FUSSING)
(LOUD ROARING)
(CRYING MUFFLED)
(CREATURE SNARLING QUIETLY)
(FEEDBACK WHINING)
(WHINING CONTINUES)
(CREATURE SNARLING)
(CREATURE SCREECHES)
(WHINING STOPS)
- (GASPS)
- LEE: Shh...
(ALOUD) It's okay. It's okay.
You're safe.
They can't hear us.
It worked.
You just need to rest now.
Where are they?
I'll find them.
No, she was with me.
She was with me, and...
then I had to go and do laundry, and...
He was with you. How did he...
Rockets.
So he'd still be there.
- I'm sure he is.
- He knows to wait for you.
And she is...
She's smart. She'll have found a place.
They know what to do.
(BABY COOING)
It's a boy.
I could've carried him.
He was so heavy, wasn't he?
I can still...
I can still feel the weight in my arms.
Small, but
so heavy.
(SOFTLY) And my hands were free.
I was carrying the bag,
but my hands were free.
You have to stop.
So, I could've carried him.
I should've carried him.
Who are we
if we can't protect them?
Who are we?
You have to protect them.
Promise me
you will protect them.
(WATER TRICKLING)
(WATER RUNNING)
Don't worry...
Don't worry... he'll come for us.
(WATER RUNNING)
(SNARLING SOFTLY)
(BABY COOING)
(BABY GURGLES)
(CREATURE HISSING)
(GROWLING)
We can't stay here.
We need to go.
He'll come for us.
He will come for us.
He'll come for you!
No, you're wrong.
He told me!
Don't move.
Stop.
(CLANGING)
(PANTING)
(GASPING)
(GASPS)
(METAL CREAKING)
(GROWLING)
(ROARING)
(FEEDBACK WHINING)
(ROARING ANGRILY)
(FEEDBACK WHINING CONTINUES)
(PAINED SCREECHING AND SNARLING)
(CREATURE SHRIEKING)
(SNARLING)
(PANTING)
Are you okay?
You okay?
(DISTANT SNARLING)
(RUSTLING)
Let's get to the truck.
(SNARLING)
- Dad!
- (GASPS)
(GROWLING)
(FEEDBACK WHINING)
(WHINING CONTINUES)
(WHINING STOPS)
(SNARLING)
(AX THUDS)
I
I love
I love you.
I
I have
I have always
I have always loved
I have always loved you.
(SCREAMING)
(SNARLING)
(SCREECHING)
(SOBBING QUIETLY)
(ROARING IN DISTANCE)
(CLACKING)
(RUMBLING IN DISTANCE)
(BABY COOING SOFTLY)
(THUDDING)
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
(SNARLING)
(HISSING)
(CLACKING)
(TELEVISION STATIC)
(TELEVISION STATIC CONTINUES)
(SHRIEKS)
(GASPS)
(LOW SNARLING)
(FEEDBACK WHINING)
(FEEDBACK WHINING CONTINUES)
(CREATURE SQUEALING)
(WAILING LOUDLY)
(FEEDBACK AMPLIFIED)
(SCREECHING)
(FEEDBACK STOPS)
(ROARING AND SNARLING)
(FAINT RUMBLING)
(COOING)